 export const questions = [
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "What is the name of the first book?",
        "answer": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher`s Stone",
        "variants": [
            "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
            "Harry Potter and the Philosopher`s Stone",
            "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
            "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What creature is Aragog?",
        "answer": "Acromantula",
        "variants": [
            "Acromantula",
            "Dog",
            "Monkey",
            "Bird"
        ]
    },
     {
         "id": 2,
         "question": "What was Hagrid's pet dog called?",
         "answer": "Fang",
         "variants": [
             "Dean",
             "Elzo",
             "Fang",
             "Max"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 3,
         "question": "Name the centaur who taught at Hogwarts.",
         "answer": "Firenze",
         "variants": [
             "Bane",
             "Firenze",
             "Ronan",
             "Magorian"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 4,
         "question": "How many people started hogwarts?",
         "answer": "4",
         "variants": [
             "4",
             "2",
             "6",
             "9"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 5,
         "question": "... Granger",
         "answer": "Hermione",
         "variants": [
             "Lavender",
             "Hermione",
             "Luna",
             "Elize"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 6,
         "question": "How many brothers does Ronald Wesley have?",
         "answer": "5",
         "variants": [
             "3",
             "1",
             "9",
             "5"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 7,
         "question": "Who is the publisher of the \"Juggler\"?",
         "answer": "Xenophilius Lovegood",
         "variants": [
             "Lucius Malfoy",
             "Cornelius Fudge",
             "Arthur Wesley",
             "Xenophilius Lovegood"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 8,
         "question": "Who is Harry's best friend?",
         "answer": "Ron Wesley",
         "variants": [
             "Neville Longbottom",
             "Dean Thomas",
             "Ron Wesley",
             "Draco Malfoy"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 9,
         "question": "What was the name of Lord Voldemort's loyal snake?\n",
         "answer": "Nagini",
         "variants": [
             "Nagini",
             "Ellen",
             "Morgan",
             "Nina"
         ]
     },
     {
         "id": 10,
         "question": "Who killed Dobby by throwing a knife at him?",
         "answer": "Bellatrix Lestrange",
         "variants": [
             "Avery",
             "Severus Snape",
             "Mulciber",
             "Bellatrix Lestrange"
         ]
     }
 ];
